Office of the President Mary Maples Dunn Files, 1985-1995
Smith College Archives
- SERIES IV. ADMINISTRATIVE ISSUES, (11 document boxes / 4.6 linear feet)
  - Persian Gulf War 1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    See also Series III. Academic Programs-Junior Year Abroad-General-Gulf War -and- Series IX. Committees & Boards-Energy Conservation Committee, Ad hoc
  - Political Correctness
    See also Series VI. Alumnae-Individuals. There are a number of letters from alums asking about the topic, and many variations on the same response from MMD.
    - -General 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - -Alumnae Correspondence 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Racism 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Racism Jan-Apr 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Racism May-Dec 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Racism Jan-Mar 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Racism Apr-Dec 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Racism 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Racism 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Research Questionnaires 1985-1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Roundtables
    - -Campus Communications 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - -Curriculum 1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - -Enrollment Management Apr 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - -Social Life Nov 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - -Smith's Future Feb 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Seatbelts 1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Secondary Education 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - South Africa
    - -General 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - -General Jan-May 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - -General Jun-Dec 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -General 1987-1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -Background Information Packet 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - -Correspondence with Corporations 1985-Jun 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - -Correspondence with Corporations Jul-Nov 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - -Correspondence with Corporations 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - -Information from Other Colleges 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - -Princeton Material 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - -Scholarships 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - -Student Protest
      - -General 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - -Alumnae Correspondence 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - -Faculty Correspondence 1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - -Student and Parent Correspondence 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - -Miscellaneous Correspondence 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Telephone System 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Town and Gown Relations
    - -General 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - -General 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - -Academy of Music 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - -Academy of Music 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - -Academy of Music 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - -Academy of Music 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - -Citizen's Scholarship Foundation 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - -Civil Rights Advisory Board 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - -Clarke School for the Deaf 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - -Clarke School for the Deaf 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - -Clarke School for the Deaf 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - -Ad hoc Committee on Attracting and Retaining High-Quality Staff 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - -Forbes Library 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - -Greater Holyoke Partnership (Box 10)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Foundations-MacArthur Fdn and Pew Charitable Trusts
    - -League of Women Voters 1985-1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - -Northampton Center for the Arts 1987-1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - -Northampton Chamber of Commerce 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - -Northampton Honor Court 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - -Northampton Public Schools 1986-1990, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - -Northampton State Hospital 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - -Pioneer Valley Ballet 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - -Valley 2000 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Wedgwood Commemorative China 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Women's Education
    - -General 1985-1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - -Elizabeth Tidball 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- SERIES V. ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICES, (22 document boxes / 9.1 linear feet)
  The files are arranged alphabetically by the most recent name of the office.
  Approximately 7 document boxes (3 linear feet) of Development material is open for research. Due to the sensitive nature of the development process, however, there is a large collection of material which will be closed to researchers for a minimum of seventy-five years.
  The Administrative Offices series is the largest series in the Dunn Files. It includes correspondence and reports from individual offices as well as newspaper clippings and other general information about their activities and functions. There may also be useful information in the Buildings and Grounds series about the buildings in which the various offices were housed. Development comprises the largest section of the Administrative Offices series.
  - Academic Computing Center
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Information Systems
  - Admissions (Box 1)
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -General 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -General 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -General 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -General 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -General 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -General 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -General 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -Alumnae-Related Candidates 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -Asia Recruitment Trip (Box 1)
      See Series V.Administrative Offices-Development-Asia Development and Recruitment Trip
    - -Brain Storming Sessions 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - -Guston Dinner, October 1986 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -Minority Students 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -Southwest Strategy Organizer 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Advancement
    See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development -and- Series IX. Committees & Boards-Advancement Committee
    - -General 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -Snelling, Kolb and Kuhnle Implementation Plan 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action
    - -General 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -Management Workshop [Folder 1] 23-24 Aug 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -Management Workshop [Folder 2] 23-24 Aug 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Officer Search 1987-1988 (Box 2)
      - -General 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - -Student Dissent (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Business Manager
    See also Series V.Administrative Offices-Controller (Office of the Business Manager eliminated in 1992-1993)
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -General 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Campus Safety 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Career Development Office
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -General 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -Internships 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -Seven Sisters Project: The Great Balancing Act 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chapel
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - -General 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - -General 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - -Farris Report 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - -Jewish Life 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - -Visiting Committee 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - -Visiting Committee 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - -Visiting Committee 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chief Financial Officer and Treasurer
    - -Annual Reports 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -General 1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - -General Jan-May 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -General Jun-Dec 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - -General 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - -General 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - -General 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - -Budget 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Budget 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -Meeting Agendas
      - -Larry Selgelid 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - -Charles Johnson 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - -Ruth Constantine 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - College Relations
    - -Annual Reports 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -General 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -General 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - -General 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -General 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - -General 1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - -Calendar Office 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - -Cultural Diversity Brochure 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - -Maguire Associates 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - -Meeting Agendas
      - -Janet McNeil 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - -Mary Reutener 1987, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - -NewsSmith 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Communications Systems (Box 6)
    See Series V.Administrative Offices-Information Systems
  - Controller 1986, 1990, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dean of the College
    - -Annual Reports 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -General 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -General 1989-1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - -Assistant Dean for Minority Affairs 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - -Assistant Dean for Minority Affairs 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - -Assistant Dean for Student Affairs 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - -Farris Report 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - -Freshman Orientation 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - -Housing Lottery 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1985-1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - -Self-Study and Retreat 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Dean of Enrollment and Management
    - -Annual Reports 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - -General 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -General 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dean of the Faculty
    - -Annual Reports 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - -General 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - -General 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - -Associate Dean 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - -Dean for Curriculum and Faculty Development
      - -General 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - -Meeting Agendas 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - -Five Year Report 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - -Meeting Agendas (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - -Minority Faculty 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - -Structure Review 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Development
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - -General 1987-1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - -Campaign for Smith
      - -General 1985-Jun 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - -General Jul 1987-Jun 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - -General Jul 1988-Dec 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - -General 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - -Congratulatory Letters 1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - -Corporate Campaign Committee 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - -Corporate Campaign Committee undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - -PMI Telefund 1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - -Thank-You Letters to Opening Hostesses 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - -Capital Campaign (Future) 1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - -Corporations
      - -Bank of Boston 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - -Bank of New England 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - -Bay Bank 1986-1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - -Chemical Bank 1986-1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - -CIGNA Corporation 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - -Citicorp 1985-1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - -Combustion Engineering 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - -Connecticut National Bank 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - -GTE 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - -Heritage-NIS Bank for Savings 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - -Honeywell Bull 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - -Kollmorgen Corporation 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - -New England Electric System 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - -Northeast Utilities 1985-1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - -Packaging Corporation of America 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - -Philip Morris 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - -Miscellaneous Corporations A-Z ca. 1985-1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - -Deferred Gifts & Bequests 1987 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - -Emerson-Lewis Fund 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - -Faculty Grants Council 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - -Foundations
      - -General ca. 1985-1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - -Aetna Foundation 1985-1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - -Alden Trust 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - -Commonwealth Fund 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - -Dana Foundation 1985-Apr 1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - -Dana Foundation Apr-Dec 1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - -Dana Foundation 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - -Dana Foundation 1990 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - -Dana Foundation ca. 1991-1995 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - -Ford Foundation 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - -Ford Foundation 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - -Ford Foundation 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - -General Electric Foundation 1985-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - -Glenmede Trust Company 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
        See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Foundations-Pew Charitable Trusts
      - -Harper Foundation 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - -Hazen Foundation 1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - -Hewlett Foundation 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - -Hewlett Foundation 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - -Johnson Endeavor Foundation 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - -Keck Foundation 1985-1990 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - -Keck Foundation 1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - -Keck Foundation 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - -[Ada Howe] Kent Foundation 1985-1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - -Kresge Foundation 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - -Kresge Foundation 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - -Kresge Foundation ca. 1990-1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - -Littauer Foundation 1988-1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - -Luce Foundation
        - -General Mar 87-Feb 88 (Box 12, Folder 6)
        - -General Mar 88-Dec 90 (Box 12, Folder 7)
        - -General ca. 1991-1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
        - -Luce Scholarship 1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - -MacArthur Foundation 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - -McCune Foundation 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - -Mellon Foundation 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - -Mellon Foundation 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - -Mellon Foundation 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - -Mellon Foundation 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - -National Science Foundation 1985-Jun 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - -National Science Foundation Jul 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - -National Science Foundation 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - -Norton Company Foundation 1986-1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - -Pew Charitable Trusts 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
        See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Foundations-Glenmede Trust Company
      - -Pew Charitable Trusts 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - -Pew Charitable Trusts 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - -Pittsburgh Foundation 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - -Robison Foundation 1990-1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - -Saint Paul Foundation 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - -Schultz Foundation 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - -Schumann Foundation 1985-1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - -Shell Companies Foundation 1985-1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - -Surdna Foundation 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - -Miscellaneous Foundations A-H ca. 1985-1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - -Miscellaneous Foundations J-P ca. 1985-1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - -Miscellaneous Foundations Q-Z ca. 1985-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - -Gift Crediting and Reporting Policy 1985-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - -Government Agencies
      - -General 1987-1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        See also Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations
      - -FIPSE 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - -Jill Ker Conway Fund for Research and Teaching on Women's Experience (Box 14)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Foundations-Fisher Foundation and Harper Foundation
    - -Meeting Agendas-MMD and Charlotte Heartt 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - -Meeting Agendas-MMD and Charlotte Heartt 1990-1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - -Parents Fund 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - -Special Projects
      See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Campaign for Smith
      - -Academic Computing undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - -Five-College Program in Coastal and Marine Sciences 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - -Jewish Studies 1986 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - -Museum of Art undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - -NPRC 1987 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - -Spectrum
      - -General ca. 1985-1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - -Fall 1985-Class Visits 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - -Spring 1986-Class Visits 1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - -Fall 1986-Class Visits 1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - -Spring 1987-Class Visits 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - -Fall 1987-Class Visits 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - -Spring 1988-Class Visits 1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - -Fall 1988-Class Visits 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - -Spring 1989-Class Visits 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - -Fall 1989-Class Visits 1989 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - -Spring 1990-Class Visits 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - -Fall 1990-Class Visits 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - -Fall 1991-Class Visits 1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - -Spring 1993-Class Visits 1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Environmental Health and Safety 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Financial Aid
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - -General 1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - -General 1986 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - -General 1987 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - -General 1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - -General 1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - -General 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - -General 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - -General 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - -Director Search 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - -Need Blind Admissions Feb-Jun 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      See also Series V. Admin. Offices-Admissions
    - -Need Blind Admissions Jul-Dec 1990, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - -Office Methods Ltd. Report 1985 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Health Services
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - -General 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - -General 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - -Aids (Box 16)
  - Human Resources
    - -General 1985-1992 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Personnel Policy Board
    - -Benefits (Box 17)
      - -General 1985-1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - -Dental 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - -Leave Plans 1985-1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - -Medical 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        See also Series IX. Committees & Boards- Medical Benfits Review Committee.
      - -Medical 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - -Medical 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - -Medical 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - -Compensation and Classification Plan 1985-1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - -Staff Counts 1985-1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Information Systems
    - -Annual Reports 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - -General 1985-1989 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - -General 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - -General 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1988, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - -Database Manual (Box 17)
      See Series IX. Committees & Boards-Registration and Standardization of Institutional Data
    - -Reorganization 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Institutional Affairs (Box 18)
    - -General 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - -General 1990-1992, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - -Departmental Planning 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Institutional Research 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Institutional Research 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Institutional Research 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Libraries
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - -Annual Reports 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - -Annual Reports 1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - -General 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - -General 1989-1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - -College Archives & Sophia Smith Collection 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - -College Archives & Sophia Smith Collection 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - -College Archives & Sophia Smith Collection 1989-1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - -Friends of the Library 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - -Hillyer Art Library 1986-1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - -Josten Performing Arts Library 1989, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - -Mortimer Rare Book Room 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - -Young Science Library 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Museum of Art
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - -Annual Reports 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - -Annual Reports 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - -Annual Reports 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - -General 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - -General 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - -General 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - -General 1993 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - -General 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - -Antwerp Symposium 1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1988-1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Personnel (Box 20)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Human Resources
  - Physical Plant
    - -Annual Reports 1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - -Annual Reports 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - -General 1985-1989 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - -General 1990 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - -General 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - -Asbestos 1985-1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - -Housekeeping 1987-1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Planning and Research (Box 21)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Institutional Research
  - President's Office
    - -General 1985-1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - -Assistant to the President for Campus Planning 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - -Christmas Cards 1985-1986, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - -Circulars 1985-1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - -Circulars 1991-1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - -Five Year Report 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      See also Series IX. Cttees & Bds-Senior Staff-Retreat-1990
    - -Goals 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - -Management by Walking Around 1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - -President's Reports
      - -Final Drafts 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - -Rough Drafts 1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - -Rough Drafts 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - -Trend Topics 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Registrar 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Registrar 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Rental Properties 1985-1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Residence and Dining Services
    - -Annual Reports 1985, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - -General 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - -General 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - -General 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - -Dining Consolidation (Box 22)
      See Series IX. Committees & Boards-Strategic Planning Committees-Dining
  - Smith College Press [proposed] 1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Special Needs Services 1989-1993 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer (Box 22)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Chief Financial Officer and Treasurer
- SERIES VI. ALUMNAE, (7 document boxes / 2.9 linear feet)